Every developer knows this feeling...
Context switching. It's the silent killer of deep work.
You're in the zone, then - terminal, browser, Slack, back to code.
By the time you're back, the thought is gone.
What if your computer just... helped?
[Antigravity IDE - Developer typing getUserData()]
Meet VibeCat. It's been watching.
[VibeCat]: "Hey - I noticed a potential null check
missing on line 47. Want me to add it?"
It didn't wait to be asked. It just... noticed.
[Developer]: "Yeah, go ahead."
[Overlay: Analyzing... Planning fix...
Executing... Step 1/2]
guard let user = user else
[VibeCat]: "Done! Null check added.
Want me to run the tests?"
No silence. No mystery. Every step, narrated.
Proactive. Transparent. Yours.
[Developer]: "Hey, can you find some focus music?"
[Overlay: Focusing Chrome... [CDP]
Opening YouTube...]
[Overlay: Searching "lo-fi focus music"
Starting playback... [Keyboard: Space]]
Chrome. YouTube. Search. Play.
Four apps, one sentence.
[Chrome opens, YouTube searches,
first result selected, video starts]
[VibeCat]: "There you go - lo-fi beats to code by.
I'll keep it going in the background."
It didn't open a dialog. It didn't ask for a URL.
It just handled it.
Across every app. Without breaking your flow.
[Terminal - Developer just ran 'ls']
[VibeCat]: "ls -la would show hidden files
and permissions too - want me to run it?"
[Developer]: "Do it."
[Overlay: Focusing Terminal... [AX]
Typing command...]
[Overlay: Focus lost - wrong window]
It missed. That happens. Here's what's different.
[Overlay: Retrying... [Attempt 2/3]
Re-focusing Terminal [CDP fallback]]
[Overlay: Retyping: ls -la
Executing... Verifying result... [Vision check]]
[VibeCat]: "Got it. Notice the dot-files now showing?
There's a .env in there you might want to check."
It retried. It verified. It explained.
No crash report, no silent failure.
It fails gracefully. Then it fixes itself.
Under the hood: a native Swift client on macOS
captures your screen and voice.
It streams to a Go backend on Cloud Run.
Gemini Live API handles the conversation
and decides when to act.
Five precise navigator tools: text entry, hotkeys,
app focus, URL open, type-and-submit.
Triple-source grounding: Accessibility tree,
Chrome DevTools, and live screenshots.
It doesn't guess. It confirms.
[GCP Console: Cloud Run services live]
Deployed on Google Cloud Run.
Always on. Zero cold-start drama.
[VibeCat]: "I'll be here when you need me.
Or before you need me."
VibeCat - Your Proactive Desktop Companion
github.com/Two-Weeks-Team/vibeCat
Built for the Gemini Live Agent Challenge 2026