VibeCat — Your Proactive Desktop Companion
🐱 "Hey! How about some relaxing music while you work?"
👤 "Yeah, play it."
🔍 LOOK: Capturing screen for vision analysis...
🎯 DECIDE: First search result detected at (497, 540)
🖱️ MOVE: Cursor smoothly animating to target...
👆 CLICK: Playing "Coding Lofi" on YouTube Music
✅ VERIFY: Music is playing! Enjoy your coding session.
🐱 VibeCat observes your code in Antigravity IDE
💡 "This code could use better documentation"
Background music continues playing throughout...
🔍 LOOK: Analyzing Antigravity window...
🖱️ MOVE: Cursor → Gemini Chat panel
⌨️ TYPE: "Enhance the comments for this code"
✅ Gemini AI processes the request
🐱 VibeCat switches to Terminal
🔍 LOOK: Capturing Terminal screen...
🖱️ MOVE: Cursor → Terminal input
⌨️ TYPE: go vet ./...
✅ VERIFY: Lint check passed — no issues found
📐 Architecture: Swift Client → Cloud Run Gateway → Gemini Live API
Vision-Based Control: LOOK → DECIDE → MOVE → CLICK → VERIFY
VibeCat — Observe. Suggest. Wait. Act. Verify.
Built for the Gemini Live Agent Challenge 2026
github.com/Two-Weeks-Team/vibeCat