VibeCat — Your Proactive Desktop Companion
"Hey! Good to see you. How about some relaxing background music while you work?"
"Yes, play it."
Vision-based control: LOOK → DECIDE → MOVE → CLICK → VERIFY
"Meow~ Music is playing! Enjoy your coding session."
Music continues in the background throughout the demo
ACT 2: Proactive Code Enhancement
VibeCat reads your code in Antigravity IDE
CLICK+TYPE: "Enhance the comments" in Gemini Chat
"Done! I've typed 'Enhance the comments' into Antigravity."
"Nya~ Don't forget to save data to sessionCache!"
Gemini AI improves code documentation
Enhancement complete — documentation added
ACT 3: Terminal Automation
VibeCat switches to Terminal
go vet ./... executed — lint check passed
"Running go vet! Checking for lint issues."
Architecture: Swift Client → Cloud Run Gateway → Gemini Live API
Google Cloud Platform: Cloud Run + Firestore + Cloud Logging
OBSERVE → SUGGEST → WAIT → ACT → VERIFY
Two Weeks Team — VibeCat