VibeCat — Technical Architecture & GCP Deployment
Swift Client → Realtime Gateway → Gemini Live API
macOS Client: Screen Capture + Accessibility Navigator (80+ key codes)
Realtime Gateway: WebSocket + 5 FC Tools + pendingFC Queue
Self-Healing Engine: Max 2 retries with alternative grounding
ADK Orchestrator: Vision Verification + Navigator Escalation
Google Cloud Run — Live Production Services
realtime-gateway: WebSocket + Gemini Live session management
adk-orchestrator: Vision analysis + confidence escalation
Firestore: Session state + Action replay persistence
Cloud Logging: Real-time observability + OTEL traces
Secret Manager: Gemini API keys + secure configuration
OBSERVE → SUGGEST → WAIT → ACT → VERIFY
Built on Google Cloud with Gemini Live API